var questions = [
    {
        question: "In JavaScript, what is a block of code called that is used to perform a specific task?",
        choices: ["Function", "Declaration", "String", "Variable"],
        correctAnswer: "Function"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a JavaScript element that represents either TRUE or FALSE values?",
        choices: ["Boolean", "RegExp", "Condition", "Event"],
        correctAnswer: "Boolean"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the element called that can continue to execute a block of code as long as the specified condition remains TRUE?",
        choices: ["Repeater", "Loop", "Debugger", "Clone"],
        correctAnswer: "Loop"
    },
    {
        question: "String values must be enclosed within ____ when being assigned to variables.",
        choices: ["commas", "curly brackets", "quotes", "parenthesis"],
        correctAnswer: "quotes"
    },
    {
        question: "A very useful tool for used during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:",
        choices: ["Javascript", "terminal / bash", "for loops", "console log"],
        correctAnswer: "console log"
    },
    {
        question: "Commonly used data types DO NOT include:",
        choices: ["strings", "booleans", "alerts", "numbers"],
        correctAnswer: "alerts"
    },
    {
        question: "The condition in an if / else statement is enclosed within ____.",
        choices: ["quotes", "curly brackets", "parentheses", "square brackets"],
        correctAnswer: "parentheses"
    },
    {
        question: "Arrays in Javascript can be used to store ____.",
        choices: ["numbers and strings", "other arrays", "booleans", "all of the above"],
        correctAnswer: "all of the above"
    },
    {
        question: "String values must be enclosed within ____ when being assigned to variables.",
        choices: ["commas", "curly brackets", "quotes", "parenthesis"],
        correctAnswer: "quotes"
    },
    {
        question: "A very useful tool for used during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:",
        choices: ["Javascript", "terminal / bash", "for loops", "console log"],
        correctAnswer: "console log"
    },


];